GAVIN FERIANCEK

- (252) 435-7547
- Suffolk, Virginia 23435
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/gavin-feriancek/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Hi, I'm Gavin. Originally from Minnesota, I'm now a resident of the southern Hampton Roads area in Virginia. I'm currently working on transitioning into a Software Engineering role with the help of **Rithm School**.

In previous roles, I've monitored warehouse production and operations, ensuring smooth workflows. I've also been instrumental in resolving any issues that arise, employing effective escalation strategies when necessary. Experience working with robots/machinery on production lines has honed problem-solving skills.

EDUCATION

Rithm School
San Francisco, CA • Expected in 08/2024

Bootcamp: Software Engineering

WORK HISTORY

Keurig Dr Pepper, Inc. - Production Operator Windsor, VA • 08/2023 - 03/2024

- Improved production efficiency by optimizing machine settings and conducting routine maintenance.
- Enhanced product quality by implementing rigorous quality control measures and identifying areas for improvement.
- Reduced downtime with proactive troubleshooting and timely resolution of equipment issues.

Amazon - Warehouse Worker Suffolk, VA • 01/2023 - 07/2023

- Loaded, unloaded, and moved material to and from storage and production areas.
- Checked packages and merchandise for damage and notified vendors.
- Learned various roles to assist team by swapping positions based on business needs.

Target - Control Center Technician Suffolk, VA • 07/2019 - 08/2022

- Usage of Excel and work specific programs to track/archive building production metrics. Regular updates provided to management.
- Monitored radio traffic, forwarding issues to maintenance and management as needed
- Assisted with escalations by submitting tickets to third party/internal systems as needed. Provided detailed notes, such as timeframes, total downtime, affected areas, etc to management.
- Assisted with organizing building workflow by ensuring FIFO.
- Monitored key production equipment (conveyor lines, item sorters, etc) via cameras. Solved any issues that arose and involved maintenance when necessary.